math_problems = [
    {
        "level": 1,
        "problem": "What is 1 + 1?",
        "answer": 2,
        "answer_choices": [2, 3, 4, 5]
    },
    {
        "level": 1,
        "problem": "What is 2 + 2?",
        "answer": 4,
        "answer_choices": [2, 3, 4, 5]
    },
    {
        "level": 1,
        "problem": "What is 3 + 3?",
        "answer": 6,
        "answer_choices": [2, 5, 4, 6]
    },
    {
        "level": 1,
        "problem": "What is 4 + 4?",
        "answer": 8,
        "answer_choices": [2, 7, 8, 9]
    },
    {
        "level": 1,
        "problem": "What is 5 + 5?",
        "answer": 10,
        "answer_choices": [9, 10, 11, 12]
    },
    {
        "level": 1,
        "problem": "What is 6 + 6?",
        "answer": 12,
        "answer_choices": [6, 10, 12, 14]
    },
    {
        "level": 2,
        "problem": "What is 1 * 1?",
        "answer": 1,
        "answer_choices": [1, 2, 3, 4]
    },
    {
        "level": 2,
        "problem": "What is 2 * 2?",
        "answer": 4,
        "answer_choices": [1, 2, 3, 4]
    },
    {
        "level": 2,
        "problem": "What is 3 * 3?",
        "answer": 9,
        "answer_choices": [10, 20, 9, 12]
    },
    {
        "level": 2,
        "problem": "What is 4 * 4?",
        "answer": 16,
        "answer_choices": [16, 20, 13, 14]
    },
    {
        "level": 2,
        "problem": "What is 5 * 5?",
        "answer": 25,
        "answer_choices": [15, 25, 30, 20]
    },
    {
        "level": 2,
        "problem": "What is 6 * 6?",
        "answer": 36,
        "answer_choices": [10, 36, 30, 35]
    },
    {
        "level": 2,
        "problem": "What is 9 * 9?",
        "answer": 81,
        "answer_choices": [91, 18, 81, 112]
    },
    {
        "level": 2,
        "problem": "What is 10 * 10?",
        "answer": 100,
        "answer_choices": [100, 200, 30, 50]
    }
]
